var characterQList = [
  {
    Question: "How much resin is required to reap the rewards of a world boss?",
    A: "20",
    B: "40",
    C: "60",
    D: "180",
    ANS: "B",
  },
  {
    Question: "Which of the following characters did NOT receive a new costume as of 2.7?",
    A: "Barbara",
    B: "Jean",
    C: "Ningguang",
    D: "Traveler",
    ANS: "D",
  },
  {
    Question: "Which of the following is the name of Xiangling's auto attack?",
    A: "Dough-Fu",
    B: "Guoba Attack",
    C: "Chef's Secret",
    D: "Crossfire",
    ANS: "A",
  },
  {
    Question: "What ascension material is required to ascend Xiao?",
    A: "Shivada Jade",
    B: "Everflame Seed",
    C: "Juvenile Jade",
    D: "Runic Fang",
    ANS: "C",
  },
  {
    Question: "This 5-star character was featured on the first Standard Banner Cover Art in Patch 1.0",
    A: "Qiqi",
    B: "Jean",
    C: "Keqing",
    D: "Mona",
    ANS: "B",
  },
  {
    Question: "How many Gemstones are required to ascend a character to 80-90?",
    A: "9",
    B: "4",
    C: "6",
    D: "8",
    ANS: "C",
  },
  {
    Question: "How many character ascension materials are required to level a character from 1 to 90?",
    A: "40",
    B: "42",
    C: "44",
    D: "46",
    ANS: "D",
  },
  {
    Question: "Which of the following is the name of Yelan's Elemental Skill?",
    A: "Necessary Calculation",
    B: "Depth-Turn Control",
    C: "Precise Shot",
    D: "Lingering Lifeline",
    ANS: "D",
  },
  {
    Question: "What AR level is required to ascend a character from 70 to 80?",
    A: "30",
    B: "35",
    C: "40",
    D: "50",
    ANS: "C",
  },
  {
    Question: "Which of the following is the name of Amber's Constellation 6?",
    A: "It Burns!",
    B: "Wildfire",
    C: "Precise Shot",
    D: "Sharpshooter",
    ANS: "B",
  },

];

